Gathered together from the cosmic reaches of the universe.
Here in this great hall of justice
are the most powerful
forces of good ever assembled.
Superman,
Batman and Robin,
Wonder Woman,
Aquaman,
and Meg.
Dedicated to truth,
justice and peace for all mankind.
Hey, Quagmire,
what've you got there?
It's the new Sports Illustrated
Swimsuit Issue. Check it out.
Those swimsuit issues don't
excite me like they used to.
I've been spoiled by internet porn.
- It's true.
- Totally.
What do you mean internet porn?
You uhh... don't know about internet porn?
Don't know what?
I'm not really a computer guy.
Quagmire, I would think you,
of all people,
would know about internet porn.
They got like thousands, literally
millions of naked pictures on the internet.
What?
And videos! Thousands of them!
You guys are messing with me.
Quagmire, you don't use the Internet?
You mean that crappy dial-up thing?
It's a pain in the ass!
No I don't use the damn internet!
I thought that was for nerds!
Why didn't you guys tell me!
Oh yeah, you can even see Tonya Harding's honeymoon video on there.
I mean... It's gross,
but it's like famous gross.
You know, these women don't compare to
the old swimsuit issues with Kathy Ireland.
Yeah she had it going on!
You know, Horace still has one of those old
beer promotional cutouts of her from like
1994, in the backroom.
Don't you, Horace?
Hey, you mean this thing?
I was about to throw it out.
If anyone wants it, it's theirs.
в™Є Suddenly,
life has new meaning to me. в™Є
в™Є There's beauty up above and
things we never take notice of. в™Є
в™Є You wake up and suddenly
you're in love. в™Є
I'm taking you home with me.
Hey Dad.
Where you going with that cutout?
Hey kids, this is Kathy.
We're designing lifestyle products together.
It's completely legitimate,
but don't tell your mother.
I had a great time today at the museum.
You were the most beautiful woman there.
You know... Lois won't be home
from groceries for a while.
I have an idea.
Knock knock, anyone in the bathroom?
I love the time we spend together,
you know that?
Hey Kathy, guess what?
I'm out... under the table,
right now... I'm out.
- Peter!
- Oh no.
What the hell is going on?
I sent you to pick up dinner an hour ago!
What are you doing with that cutout?
You know what, Lois,
I'm glad you found out!
I can't carry on this charade anymore!
I have an announcement to make.
No no, I'll do it, I'll do it.
I know I been able to keep this a secret.
But Kathy and I
are not actually working on
a project together.
We're... in love!
You're an idiot.
My lawyer will call your lawyer.
Ugh, this is stupidest thing
he's done since he got
in that turf war with that cat.
Hey shut up!
Now kids, you don't have to
call her Mom right away,
but I do want you guys to get along.
Just give her a chance,
I think you'll like it.
Maybe she'll let us do things
that Lois won't let us do.
Yeah! Hey Mom,
can I pull my pants down?
If she doesn't answer,
does that mean yes?
That's what I been going with.
Yay! Ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha...
- I want to get in on that!
- Ha ha ha ha ha ha...
Mine's better, mine's better, mine's better!
Oh, hello Lois...
I would've thought you would've
moved in with your mother by now.
No Peter, I'm just pretty much letting this run its course.
Well I'm sorry you're handling this so poorly,
but have you seen Kathy?
We were gonna go get our passports renewed.
Uh Chris took her into his room
about ten minutes ago.
What? That whore!
She's betrayed me worse than
Lady Macbeth betrayed Duncan!
I uhh...
I don't know Shakespeare very well.
Kathy? Kathy!
There you are! Oh, don't give me that look.
You don't think I know where you been?
How dare you make a fool of me!
Did you have sex with that fat kid?
Did you? Answer me!
Oh my God,
look what you made me do!
Why did you have to provoke me?
Why did you hav...
Quagmire? Hey uh...
Nobody's seen you in days!
Hey, Peter.
I just been uhh... checking out
some of that internet porn.
You okay?
Yeah yeah I'm good I'm good I'm good...
I'm just gonna...
Go... go and check my mail over there.
You been lifting weights?
Uhh no... no...
I don't think uhh... No.
I'm... I'm sorry Peter, I gotta...
I gotta get back.
I'm sorry, Lois,
I was a fool!
I'm done with Kathy!
Can you ever forgive me?
Peter, settle down.
Yes I forgive you,
just as long as you are done
with that stupid cutout.
I just want you to know that
every time I was with her,
I was thinking of you.
Peter, stop.
Come on, I'm not in the mood.
Oh, Peter!
Oh, Lois, I've missed you! You and your
wonderful smile and your beautiful eyes
and your awesome third boob
that's on top of the other boob.
What? Oh my God!
Peter, that's not a boob, that's a lump!
A lump? Holy crap!
Peter, stop that! We're not having sex!
I just told you I have a lump!
I got a lump too and mine is easier to get rid of.
Mrs. Griffin, I've got good news.
Your test results came back negative
It appears the lump in your breast is not
"black gross boob death."
Breast cancer?
That's the layman's term, yes.
Oh, thank God.
- What a relief!
- Yeah, that was scary.
Now Mrs. Griffin, although you are
in the clear for the moment,
we need to have a look at
your family medical history
to determine your future risk.
Huh, that's curious. I didn't realize your
mother was a Holocaust survivor.
My mother? Oh no that's...
That's impossible, she's not Jewish.
According to her birth certificate, she is.
Oh my God!
Wow, breast cancer's starting
to look pretty good.
Mom, you're Jewish?
I'm sorry I never told you, dear.
When we were married,
tour father made me conceal the fact
so he could get into country clubs.
- It was the right thing to do.
- It was the right thing to do, dear.
Oh my God!
So Granda Hebrewberg
is actually Jewish?
Yes, when she moved to America,
her family changed their name.
It was originally
Hebrewberg-Moneygrabber.
That makes you Jewish, Lois,
and your children too.
Well, this kinda rocks my world.
Even more than the time
when I went to that pediatrician.
Woah, Stewie,
you're getting to be a big boy.
I think somebody is gonna be a football star.
Oh, you...
Oops, forgot your chart,
be right back.
Woah, Jason,
you're getting to be a big boy.
I think somebody is gonna be a football star.
I can't believe I fell for that line.
I actually let myself believe I could
be a doctor's wife.
You're just fat, Stewie,
silly and fat.
Thanks you for coming over, Max.
I really need some advice from
an actual Jewish person.
Oh, it's my pleasure, Lois.
I'm sure this all must be
very overwhelming.
I just don't know what to
do with this information.
I spent my whole life as a Christian.
I'll tell you what you should do with it,
absolutely nothing!
That's the problem with this world.
Too many people go overboard
with what they believe.
Like Quagmire, when he thought
he was the one getting the spin-off.
See you later, bitches.
Have fun with your stupid (bleep)
giant chicken jokes and your Conway Twitty.
Hey, why is there a moving truck
outside Cleveland's house?
Well, I wouldn't put it quite like that,
but essentially Brian's right.
Being Jewish doesn't really have to
change you or your family's life.
Wow, I guess you're right.
There's no reason things should
be any different around here.
Shalom, Jews!
Wow dad, where did you get all
that glistening chest hair?
Came with my Star of David.
Peter, what is all this?
Look, this is my way of letting you know
that I'm embracing who you are.
Oh, and I don't respond to Peter.
From now on
I want you to use my Hebrew name.
Well, I... I caution you uhh...
that becoming Jewish
doesn't happen overnight.
It's a process that involves
spiritual education and good works.
So what you're saying is that it happens overnight?
Look, Peter, I am the one
with the Jewish heritage,
and I really don't want to make
a big deal out of this.
Leave it to a Jew to take all
the fun outta being a Jew.
Now listen up, I like the hat and I
like the scarf, so we are doing this.
Kids, from now on,
this is where we will celebrate the Sabbath.
Peter, this is all unnecessary.
Our life was fine the way it was.
Check it out!
I'm one of you guys now, huh.
I'm Jewish, yeah!
Holocaust! We're number one!
Look at all these short, hairy men.
God I feel like I'm on the forest moon of Endor.
Good afternoon.
As we approach the Passover holiday,
let us remember the struggle of our people
as they labored under the yoke
of Pharaoh's despotic rule.
Hey, if anyone appreciates
a good yoke it's the Yews.
That's my Jewish laugh.
I'm working on a Jewish laugh.
Peter, I am so embarrassed right now.
Can we please just go?
- Hi, you're pretty.
- Oh, thank you.
Mom, is sodomy illegal
if you're Jewish?
I hope to so, Meg. I really do.
It's not, Lois.
It's not.
Dad, this isn't the
way to school.
Yes it is, Chris.
One of the best parts about being Jewish
is getting to take advantage
of their excellent schools.
I'm not going to no Jewish school.
Sitting around all day
with a bunch of short, hairy guys,
I feel like I'm on the forest moon of Endor.
Didn't you... didn't you make
that joke the other day?
Oh... yeah... No I was...
I wasn't sure that everybody had umm...
had heard.
And instead of lasting for one day,
the oil in the lamp lasted for eight days,
and this is why we celebrate Hanukkah.
Yeah yeah yeah, how long before we play
"Pin the eviction notice
on the black guy's door."
Now does anyone have any questions?
Yeah I have a question. What are you
gonna do when Jesus comes back
and puts a boot up your ass?
And it's also why many families
give their children eight days of presents.
Wait, did she say eight days of presents?
Yeah.
Well, this Judaism thing is
gonna be better than I thought.
Alright class,
that's all for today's lesson.
Now everyone off to gym class.
Alright, today we're gonna play soccer.
Huh, that was easy.
Hey Lois, the kids are all asleep
I suppose they are
You know what else? I picked out a sexy
little Jewish outfit for you at the store
What is that?
Oh my God Lois, if you put on this long,
thick dress right now I will lose it.
Peter, I'm not wearing that thing.
And if you put this
shawl over your head ...
Ooh, you have clunky,
unfashionable, peasant shoes?
Oh, I swear to God, Lois.
I swear to God that I would lose it.
Peter, get off me!
Tell me I don't earn as much
as your friend's husband!
Peter, stop it!
I'm going to sleep.
Fine, I'll just sit here and watch TV.
We now return to Mark Wahlberg
in "Annoyed and Confused."
What? What's going on?
I don't get it.
Man, I gotta work out.
What's going on here?
Where am I? What the... huh?
What the hell is going on here?
Huh? What?
Peter!
Dad?
What do you think you're doing, Peter?
You were raised Catholic.
If you rescind your religion,
you will spend eternity... in hell!
Oh God, I don't want that!
Then you better not fall
for all the Jewish stuff.
Oh... alright,
if that's what you think is best.
Oh wait, Dad,
before you to go, can you say:
"Peter, you must go to the Degobah System"?
Peter, you must go
to the Degobah System.
Thanks.
Anybody want toast or a bagel?
Peter, what the hell!
Lois, last night my father came to me
and reminded me
that I am a good Catholic.
If I don't rid the house of this Jewish curse,
this family is gonna go to hell!
And I won't let that happen!
Peter, you were the only one who was even
taking this thing seriously.
Jews are gross, Lois.
It's the only religion with the word 'ew' in it.
Oh, come on. You're acting
crazier than when you were
going through your Parker Lewis phase.
Peter, you ready for dinner?
Ah, that's just like the Parker Lewis episode
when Parker Lewis ate dinner.
Peter, nobody cares about your canceled show.
Lois, Parker Lewis can't lose.
Don't even try and make him lose,
because it's just gonna be
that much more embarrassing for you
when you realize that he can't lose.
Would he win in a fight with Batman?
Well, Chris, think about what you're saying.
Parker Lewis can't lose.
Heretofore, Batman can suck on that.
Suck on that? Suck on this!
TicTacs only have 1.5 calories!
Well played.
I love you, Dad.
I love you too, son.
What the... what the hell!
How do you like it? Huh?
How do you like it?
Peter, what in God's name is this?
Wait a minute,
are these pieces of Stewie's crib?
I hate it here!
Well, thanks for spending time
with me today, Mom.
I just had to get out of that house,
Peter is being such a jackass.
Lois, I think this more serious than you realize.
Don't you see what he's doing?
Oh, he's just being immature.
It's happened before and it will pass.
Lois, what Peter is doing to you is
exactly what Carter did to me for years.
He's repressing your Jewish identity!
But Mom, I don't really care
about being Jewish,
or even Christian for that matter!
I just want to be
a good person on my own.
All I'm saying is I let your father take
my Jewish identity and I've
regretted it ever since.
I don't want to see you
make the same mistake.
I don't know, Mom.
I'll think about it.
Carter, knock it off!
Come on, you know you Jew girls want that dollar!
Follow the dollar and it'll lead you to...
What... what does Jews like?
Salmon! There's salmon over here!
Is there really salmon over there?
No, you walk over there and
he squirts you with a squirt gun.
What the hell!
Are you out of your (bleep) mind?
Relax, Lois, I was aiming for the mailbox,
I'm just trying to make point
Good morning, Lois
Peter, for God sake!
I am so sorry, Mort.
No problem, Lois.
That's just how people say hello to me.
- Hey, Joe.
- Hey, Mort.
Peter, you and I are
gonna have a conversation.
- I am very angry with you.
- Geez, what's your problem?
What you did this morning was
so far outta line, I just...
Let me tell you this,
Mom was right.
I can't just sit here and let you
dump all over my heritage.
I'm not gonna make the mistake she did.
I'm Jewish and I am proud of it.
And this weekend
we're having a Passover Seder.
- You can't do that, it's Easter!
- Not in this house.
Lois, this family believes
in the Easter Bunny.
He died for our sins
in that helicopter crash.
Now, if you want to go hell, that's fine.
But don't drag the rest of us down with you
like a mentally handicapped rooster.
Good night, everybody!
Okay everyone,
this is my first time doing a Seder,
which is where we tell the story of the
Jews' escape from bondage in Egypt.
Doesn't it seem like every Jewish holiday
has to do with them escaping from stuff?
No, Chris.
And you know, tricking some bigger, more athletic people...
Uhh... Lois, not that I'm rushing you,
but when do we get to the wine drinking?
Hang on! Hang on!
Before do anything,
I'd like to say a blessing over
the candles, if I may.
Now bear with me,
I haven't had much rehearsal time.
Can't we just eat?
And now I shall continue with the prayer
And now let's move on to
the washing of the hands.
This is a very important part
of the cerem...
Hey, hey, hey!
The Easter Bunny is here!
Happy Easter!
Peter, what the hell are you doing in that...
Have you been drinking?
Not since I got out of the car.
Who here thinks I can
kick my ass?
Peter, you are not gonna ruin this
Seder. Now get outta here.
I'm sorry, kids.
I just wanted to help
Brian run for mayor.
I guess I forgot
what was really important.
Peter, just go lie down.
Alright, I'm gonna go lie down, and then I'm
gonna come back and mess up your Seder.
Alright, I'm back and
I'm much more sober.
Lois, what you're doing is wrong.
I want you to get all this
Jew food off the table.
I most certainly will not!
It's me or your religion, Lois.
I am a Catholic and I want
to live in a Catholic house.
Well, I'm a Jew and I want
live in a nicer house.
Do you really think
I should run for mayor?
Peter, you have got to stop
living in your own stupid world!
I'm sorry, but I can't be with someone who doesn't believe in Jesus.
Hey hey, heard my name!
Wow, Jesus!
Oh, you're dead now, Lois.
Jesus is gonna kill ya.
And then we gonna bury you in the
yard, next to Kathy Ireland...
Er, I mean uhh...
Nice weather we're having!
Look Peter, I thought it might
interest you to know that I'm Jewish.
What?
He's Jewish, Peter.
Jewish, like full on,
like you practice Jewey-ism?
I am a Jew.
Prove it! What's a 9% tip
on a $200 bill?
$18, which is fair...
Oh my God, it's true!
But I'm so confused.
Peter, it really doesn't matter.
Catholicism and Judaism
are not that different.
They're two sides of same coin.
In fact, the Last Supper, one of
the most iconic images of the
Catholic faith, was a Passover Seder.
And if I'm not mistaken, Islam
is also in that same spiritual family.
Uhh... Let's not muddy things up here.
The most important thing
is to treat other people
the same way you would
want to be treated.
Ooooh... an eye for an eye!
Well, Lois,
I guess I owe you an apology.
I was scared because my dad
convinced me I was going to hell.
And I was doing it to make up
for my mother's mistake.
Look, I don't know if being Jewish is
the right thing for our family.
I just wanted the chance to explore it
so I could know for sure.
But to tell you the truth,
I thought we were fine before.
But, then Jesus,
which religion should our family be?
Six to one, they are all complete crap.
Thank you!
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru